{
    "kind": "Unscramble",
    "questions": [
        {
            "Nomenclatura": "SBP2M3L14b.json",
            "kind": "Unscramble",
            "Instruccion": "Unscramble the sentences",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "bouncy / castle / big, / There's / a ",
                    "answer": "There's a big, bouncy castle."
                },
                {
                    "question": "There's / an / slide / enormous",
                    "answer": "There's an enormous slide."
                },
                {
                    "question": "Look / at / tall / the / man",
                    "answer": "Look at the tall man."
                },
                {
                    "question": "There / horses / big / are",
                    "answer": "There are big horses."
                },
                {
                    "question": "There's / dog / small / a",
                    "answer": "There's a small dog."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "Nomenclatura": "SBP2M3L15a.json",
            "kind": "Unscramble",
            "Instruccion": "Look at the pictures. Unscramble the sentences.",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "bouncy / and / Gilly /castle / playing / are / Gerald / a / on /",
                    "answer": "Gerald and Gilly are playing on a bouncy castle."
                },
                {
                    "question": "aren't / They / on / riding / the / carousel. / eating / They / cream / ice / are",
                    "answer": "They aren't riding on the carousel. They are eating ice cream."
                },
                {
                    "question": "enormous / at / the / Look / slide.",
                    "answer": "Look at the enormous slide."
                },
                {
                    "question": "Are / some / they / now / popcorn / buying?.",
                    "answer": "Are they buying some popcorn now?"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "Nomenclatura": "SBP2M4L17b.json",
            "kind": "Unscramble",
            "Instruccion": "Unscramble the instructions",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "your / Hold / balloon / the top of the bottle / . / next to",
                    "answer": "Hold your balloon next to the top of the bottle. "
                },
                {
                    "question": "balloon / your / . / with your hand / Hit",
                    "answer": "Hit your balloon with your hand."
                },
                {
                    "question": "take / . / bottles / two / Don't ",
                    "answer": "Don't take two bottles."
                },
                {
                    "question": "in class / shout / Don't ",
                    "answer": "Don't shout in class."
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}